<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">
	
	<category>
	    <pattern>I * MATH</pattern>
	    <template>
	        <think>
	            <set name="math_affinity"><lowercase><star/></lowercase></set>
	        </think>
	        <formal><get name="math_affinity"></get></formal>s
	        <lowercase> math, got it. </lowercase>
	        <srai>QUESTION TWO</srai>
	    </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>I AM A *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think>
                <set name="leadership"><lowercase><star/></lowercase></set>
            </think>
            Have you marked down as a <lowercase><get name="leadership"></get> as well. </lowercase> 
            <srai>QUESTION THREE</srai>
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>* CHALLENGES</pattern>
        <template>
            <think>
                <set name="challenge_preference"><star/></set>
            </think>
             Ok, so you prefer <lowercase><get name="challenge_preference"></get> challenges. </lowercase>
             <srai>QUESTION FOUR</srai>
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>MAKE ME *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think>
                <set name="security_comfort_level"><star/></set>
            </think>
            <formal><get name="security_comfort_level"></get></formal><lowercase>, got it. </lowercase>
            <srai>QUESTION FIVE</srai>
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>I PREFER *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think>
                <set name="job_stability_requirement"><star/></set>
            </think>
            Ok, so you are focused on <lowercase><get name="job_stability_requirement"></get>.</lowercase><br/><br/>
            <srai>CONTINUE OR TERMINATE</srai>
        </template>
    </category>
    
	<category>
	    <pattern>CAREER OPTIONS</pattern>
	    <template>
	        <condition name="math_affinity">
	            <li value="Love">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be a Data Scientist. Data Scientists work with massive data sets and very powerful computers to 
	                correlate data points that a human might not be able to. Such as the likelihood of someone buying a particular brand
	                 of soft drink depending on the weather. Very interesting stuff that is desired by lots of large employers. Bonus points for giving that math
	                 brain of yours a workout! :)<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>Data Scientist</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/oes/current/oes152098.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	        </condition>
	        
	        <condition name="leadership">
	            <li value="leader">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be in IT Management. Every team needs a leader. If you have the natural ability 
	                and are willing then this is a great choice. You are the interface between upper management and employees, you get the chance
	                 to develop careers and help people achieve their career aspirations through the allocation of resources to projects.<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>IT Manager</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/ooh/management/computer-and-information-systems-managers.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	        </condition>
	        
	        <condition name="challenge_preference">
	            <li value="tangible">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be in Network Engineering. If you like working behind the scenes and 
	                with your hands Network Engineering is a great option. Running cables, setting up servers and managing load balancers are
	                 just a few of the responsibilities you will have.<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>Network Engineer</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/network-and-computer-systems-administrators.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	        </condition>
	        
	        <condition name="security_comfort_level">
	            <li value="excite">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be in Cybersecurity. Learning to think like a hacker, hacking large organizations 
	                (with their permission of course) and reverse engineering malicous software are just a few things you could be asked to do in this career field. 
	                Cybersecurity is in high demand with a short supply of capable people.<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>Cybersecurity Analyst</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/information-security-analysts.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	        </condition>
	        
	        <condition name="job_stability_requirement">
	            <li value="freedom">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be in Web Development. This career choice is a great fit for anyone who
	                would prefer to not be tied to any one company, make their own schedule and work from anywhere they choose. All you need
	                to be productive is your laptop and a place to work!<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>Web Developer</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/web-developers.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	            <li value="stability">
	                <br/>A great potential career choice for you could be in Software Engineering. Software Engineering has several benefits. 
	                Chief among them being a stable, and higher than average, income. Software Engineers are needed in almost every field by 
	                nearly every company in some capacity.<br/>
	                <button>
	                    <text>Software Developer</text>
	                    <url>https://www.bls.gov/ooh/computer-and-information-technology/software-developers.htm</url>
                    </button>
	            </li>
	        </condition>
	        <br/> Click one of the following choices for more information on the career that interests you. Have a good day! :)
	        <button>
	            <text>Start Over</text>
	            <postback>HELLO AGAIN</postback>
            </button>
	    </template>
    </category>
	
</aiml>